Hello friends, you are watching Bala India,
Dheer. As we are going to talk about today, the
results of ICICI Bank General Insurance have come, so we will see
how their results were. If
you are a first time visitor to our channel, then subscribe to the channel and also
press the bell icon so that you can
get notifications of such upcoming videos on
time. So let's
start the video, so we will compare it for
December 2023.
For the quarter to quarter, we will compare it with September 2023
and for the year on year, we
will compare it with December 2022. So, if we
look at their sales numbers, then their sales this
time are
5175 crores. In the previous quarter, it was 5250
crores and in the last quarter, it was
4559 crores. So, here their sales have increased year on
year but have decreased a bit from quarter to quarter. Let's
talk about
expenses, so this time their expenses are
4638 crores, which was in the last quarter.  4507
crores and last in this quarter it was
crores. Talking about operating profit, this
time their operating profit is 537 crores
in the last quarter, 744 crores in the last
quarter and 454 crores in this quarter. So, the year
on year profit is good but the quarter to quarter
operating profit has come down a lot. If we
talk about their operating
profit margin, this time their
margin was only 10. In the last quarter it
was 14 and last in this quarter
it was 10, that is, it was 10. So their
year on year is fine but quarter to
quarter their margins have shrunk a lot. If we
talk about other income, this
time their other income is 37 crores. In the last quarter it was
20 crores and in this quarter it was
11 crores. If we
talk about interest, they did
not pay any interest. Regarding depreciation,
they have nothing in depreciation. Now let's talk about
their profit before tax. Their
profit before tax this time is
574 crores.  In the quarter it was 754
crores, sorry 764 crores and
in the last quarter it was 465 crores. So here year on
year their numbers are good, profit
before tax, but see the quarter to quarter
numbers, there has been a significant drop from 764 to
574. Let's talk about their net profit, so their net
profit this time is 431 crores,
in the last quarter it was 577 crores and
in the last quarter it was 353 crores. So here if you
see year on year, their net profit
numbers are good but quarter to quarter
their net profit numbers are on the weak side. So this is how
were the
Q3 results of ICI Lombard General Insurance. If you
liked the video, then like the video and also
subscribe to the channel
and press the bell icon so that
you get notifications of such upcoming videos at the right time.
If you want to watch more videos
related to this result, then
go to our playlist section, there is
a playlist of results, so
you can go to it and see, we have
made and posted videos of other companies here too.
You can go and watch it.
Thank you for watching the full video. Have a nice day.